好吧 我洗耳恭听 请说
Fine. I'll just listen. Go ahead.
布雷斯林先生
Mr. Breslin
非常规引渡条例被禁用以后
after ending extraordinary rendition
中央情报局在寻求
the Agency is looking for
另一种特殊方式来监禁那些
alternate situations for incarcerating the sort of people
犯下严重罪行的人
who commit acts so despicable
最好让他们...
they're best...
怎么说呢?
Well, how can I put it?
除掉他们?
Eliminated?
让他们消失
Disappeared.
我们在测试一个原型系统
And we're currently testing a prototype
用来关押政府不想要的犯人
to deal with people no government wants on their books.
最重要的是
But first and foremost
项目投资人要确保
the people financing this need to know
这些监狱牢不可破
these facilities are escape-proof
才会在全球进行推广
before the whole system goes online globally.
她的意思是
What she's really saying is